[Unsoiled Starlight]
[Episode 21]
[Adapted from Migu's novel
“Unsoiled Starlight” ]
[Original Writer: Shan Gu Jun]
Did you guys see the news?
Someone posted
that after using
Zhuoyuan Tech's smart home system,
they were diagnosed as being hypnotized.
That's unbelievable.
It's so absurd.
How could anyone believe such a thing?
It must be a scam.
Technically speaking,
it's not impossible.
But what company
would take such a huge risk?
Whose product did they install?
Tell us so we can avoid it.
Do they have persecution paranoia?
Tinglan,
did you hear?
Last night,
someone posted on social media,
claiming they were hypnotized
by a smart home system.
Now all fingers
are pointed at Zhuoyuan Technology.
Looks like
we might have to work overtime
with their PR team.
No way.
Zhuoyuan Tech is such a big group.
Could it be a publicity stunt?
At first,
we thought it was a marketing ploy.
But this morning,
the poster released
a clear medical report.
It seems
it's actually true.
Things on the internet
are hard to tell.
Let's wait and see.
There might be a twist.
The relationships in the previous case
are quite complex.
Lawyer Zhou, you need to communicate more
and sort it out clearly.
Next,
we will draft a legal letter
based on the PR content.
The third wave of news has been released.
Denying product issues.
Exposing Wen Jian's personal behavior.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
This legal letter...
Mr. Zhuo.
Understood.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Mr. Zhuo means
this incident
will be handled
by their internal legal team.
I'm not coming home tonight.
Don't wait up for me.
Don't skip your dinner.
[Hongzheng Law Firm]
Zhuo Yu'an!
We shouldn’t rush
a press conference.
If it's really a product issue,
we should present
a convincing data report.
Otherwise,
it's just slander and false accusations.
And I don't believe
you'd ruin your own future like that.
This must be a smear campaign
by our competitors.
[Meeting Room]
You know me.
I only do things with evidence.
[Zhuoyuan Tech Smart Home System
Press Conference]
Regarding the doubts
raised by users today
about our products,
I am here
to respond
on behalf of Zhuoyuan Tech.
We've conducted an internal review.
The issues exposed
are true.
This incident
was a personal act of revenge
by our CTO, Wen Jian.
The above actions did not involve
-What’s going on?
-the other products and users.
We'll work with Wen Jian to...
[Zhuoyuan Tech Smart Home System
Press Conference]
Are you behind that?
As you can see.
Why?
Wen Jian,
why did you do this?
You ruined yourself,
and even ruined Zhuoyuan Tech.
There’s no why.
Zhuoyuan Tech wasn't ruined by me,
but by Zhuo Yu'an.
Blame it on his indulgence
and indecision.
We'll work with the authorities
to hand Wen Jian over to the courts
and fully cooperate
with the follow-up investigation.
On behalf of the company,
I'd like to offer all our users
our sincerest apologies.
But Zhuo Yu'an shouldn't really apologize.
Wen Jian should.
[Inpatient Department]
Are you that free,
Ms. Wen?
Oh, I forgot.
You're really free.
Cut the "Ms. Wen."
Are you satisfied now?
Not really.
What are you up to next?
[Police Report Receipt]
See you in court.
Why so ruthless?
What a coincidence.
When your mother took you
to kneel before Shu Minghai,
I thought the same thing.
Shu Tinglan,
like mother, like daughter.
You both self-righteously believe
in the goodness men show.
That's why Shu Minghai
fooled you completely.
And now,
what is the outcome?
Probably,
a mother and daughter loving each other
and spending their later years in peace.
Unlike someone,
who's busy spending a fortune
to hire the best lawyers
so they don't
end up in jail later.
Hey!
I really don't get you.
When the situation was most favorable,
you said Zhuoyuan Tech was also a victim.
What if they say
you staged the whole thing?
He won't.
What spell did Zhuo Yu'an cast on you?
I'm just
telling the truth.
Hello?
Shu,
still listening?
Enough talk.
Zhuo Yu'an?
You must be exhausted.
Thank you.
Why didn't you go home?
If I fall asleep at home,
I won’t get to see you.
Let's go.
I won't go in.
I still have things to do at the company.
What's the matter?
Why so urgent?
Regulators have summoned us.
I have to be there.
Don't overthink it.
It has nothing to do with you.
I ordered food for you.
Don't skip it.
I'm leaving.
Don't skip your meal either.
Mr. Zhuo.
Someone ordered food for you.
Who ordered it?
She said
she is Mrs. Zhuo.
Thank you, Lawyer Xiao.
You're so busy,
yet you still made time to help me.
No need to be so polite.
But I never expected
they'd defend it by claiming
the data was implanted for experiments.
But fortunately,
we won the case.
After all, we have
the invincible Lawyer Xiao.
Wen Jian got hit
with administrative penalties
and a public apology.
The client is very satisfied.
I didn't expect
you and Wen Jian
to have such a deep history.
Now that it's come to this,
it's time to move on.
I'll give you two days off
to relax and unwind.
Lawyer Xiao,
what about the Tingjing Finance case?
Don't worry.
We can spare you for two days.
I'm off.
Why are you here?
Zhuoyuan Tech's in such a big mess.
Your dad wanted a talk with me.
What did he ask about?
The internal situation.
Talk properly with him.
No argument.
Look at the mess you've made.
I told you already
to pick the right partners carefully.
But you wouldn't listen.
Also,
your company's internal operations
are highly inefficient.
That tech company of yours
looks like a childish setup to me.
It's good if it collapses
during this crisis.
Come back
to my investment department already.
Are you mute?
You were so eloquent
at the press conference.
Talking about customer privacy
and trust.
You're only good at talking.
Oh,
that's enough.
Why are you yelling?
Our son finally comes home,
and all he hears is you shouting.
What's the big deal?
Why are you so angry?
Have some tea.
It's fresh.
I'm not in the mood.
Fooling around like this,
he has disgraced our family.
Drink it or not.
I should've just dumped it.
Besides,
whose face did we lose?
Yours?
Did it embarrass your old, wrinkled face?
Honestly.
When you were Yu'an's age,
you couldn't even speak English.
You guys talk.
I'm leaving.
Yu'an!
Hey.
It's bitter and astringent.
Who would want it?
Yu'an!
Don't mind your dad's nonsense.
He’s such an old fossil.
What does he know?
Mom,
it really was my fault this time.
I'll be more careful.
Alright.
Why so formal here?
Oh, right.
Tell me.
I heard from the girls at your company
that you're chasing someone.
What's her name?
What does she do?
Do you have a picture?
Let me see.
Mom,
stop checking up on me, alright?
I didn't.
That's why I'm asking you.
Alright, Mom.
When we...
When we make some progress,
I'll tell you for sure, okay?
I really have things to do.
I'll get going.
Hey…
I...
I haven’t finished talking!
Once again!
Stubborn guy.